loveandfriends.com 2004-04-01

# Love and Friends : Internet dating for thinking people . . . And it's free

free dating, dating uk, london dating, internet dating, dating agency, online dating, personals, introductions Love and Friends : Internet dating for thinking people . . . And it's free free dating, dating uk, london dating, internet dating, dating agency, online dating, personals, introductions Internet dating for thinking people . . . And it's free - the best UK dating site I've seen free dating, dating uk, london dating, internet dating, dating agency, online dating, personals, introductions  free dating dating uk london dating internet dating dating agency online dating personals introductions [Searchengineering](http://www.yuki-onna.co.uk/)

[ISP,hosting,design,online shopping](http://www.b-1st.com/) free dating, dating uk, london dating, internet dating, dating agency, online dating, personals, introductions 

|    
---|---  
  |   | 

_**A great place to meet!**_

|   |    
  |   |   |   |    
|   |  |   | __  
**__**

P **rivacy Policy**

Please read the following privacy statement to understand how loveandfriends.com will treat your personal information when you use this site. 

If loveandfriends.com changes this policy (which it may do from time to time), loveandfriends.com will make this clear in its home page, and accordingly, you will be permitted the opportunity not to accept such changes. This may mean however, that loveandfriends.com cannot provide the Service to you. 

**What information does loveandfriends.com collect?**

In order to provide the Service to you, loveandfriends.com needs to collect certain personal information about you (e.g. your e-mail address, name, etc,). When you register with loveandfriends.com, you will be required to submit information about yourself as prompted by the Service’s registration form (such information being the “Registration Data”). loveandfriends.com will store this information on its UK based computers together with any information you may provide to loveandfriends.com from time to time. 

**It is necessary for us to use this personal information.**

When you use the Site or Service, loveandfriends.com will automatically track certain information about you for purpose of internal administration and research. This information includes things like your domain name and IP address, your browser and operating system, the URL you came from, the pages you visit within the site and the URL you go to when you leave the Site. 

Loveandfriends.com will use your personal data to operate an active member directory through which other Members can contact you. If you do not wish to be included in this member directory, you may at any time contact loveandfriends.com to “opt out”. You can choose to either suspend your membership or have your details permanently deleted. 

Our site itself may also include links to other web sites. Except as expressly set out herein, loveandfriends.com shall not share personally identifiable information with the providers of such linked web sites, but may provide aggregate information regarding users to such operators - (e.g. "Dear Himalaya Trekking Co., our statistics show that 57% of loveandfriends members are interested in adventure holidays so maybe you would like to place a link on our site") . Loveandfriends.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such linked sites and hereby expressly disclaims all responsibility and liability which may arise therefrom. 

**loveandfriends is anti-spam**

loveandfriends.com discloses your personal information to third parties for the purposes of associated administration and obtaining professional advise (e.g. on the basis of research) only. loveandfriends.com does not sell, rent or trade your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your express consent.

We may send your information internationally (which may include countries outside the European Economic Area). Such other countries offer differing levels of protection of personal information, not all of which may be as high as in the UK. 

**Marketing and promotional activities are important.**

loveandfriends.com uses personal information to provide you with periodic marketing and promotional notices. This forms part of loveandfriends.com’s personalised service offering and loveandfriends.com sees this as being a significant benefit to users. However, if you do not wish to receive these services, you may at any time contact loveandfriends.com to “opt out” and loveandfriends.com would then not provide these services to you. 

**loveandfriends.com uses cookies.**

Cookies are small files, which are sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard disk. loveandfriends.com uses these cookies on a limited basis (e.g. to store your unique personal identification details given to you on registration). loveandfriends.com believes that using cookies in this way is beneficial to the efficient operation of the love and friends website.

Cookie technology also helps loveandfriends.com to determine which features and service are important to which audiences so that it may know where to invest its ongoing development and creative efforts. Other than this, loveandfriends.com does not store personal information in the cookie or use it for any other purpose. 

**loveandfriends.com complies with data protection requirements.**

loveandfriends.com complies with and is registered in accordance with data protection legislation in the UK. To allow loveandfriends.com to do this, you agree to the collection, storage and processing of your personal information by loveandfriends.com in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. 

loveandfriends.com will not disclose personal information nor edit, or disclose the contents of a user's private communications or personal information except as expressly set out herein or if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: 

(1) conform or comply with applicable law; 

(2) protect and defend the rights or property of loveandfriends.com; or 

(3) to protect the personal safety of our members or the public. 

**Security**

While loveandfriends.com strives to protect its users personal information and privacy, we do not guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. You acknowledge that you are aware of security and privacy limitations inherent to the internet environment. 

**Do you have questions?**

If you have questions or concerns about the content of this Privacy Policy or any personal information loveandfriends.com holds about you, if you wish to alter or update such information or would like to “opt out” of (or resume) receiving marketing or promotional notices or being included in the members directory, you should e-mail us at [info@loveandfriends.com](mailto:info@loveandfriends.com)
